Joseph Sciorra collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3. Italian American music, theater, poetry, and visual arts, ca. 1980-2016
  - Sicilian Band of Chicago, 1986, ca. 1986; AFC 2018/065: SR238; 1 sound cassette: analog
    Directed by: Frank Albian.
  - Sicilian oral poetry, ca. 1977-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Sicilian puppets - general, ca. 1980-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Sicilian puppets, NYC and USA, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Songs of Trinacria: A Collection of Sicilian Folk Music, afc2018065_dc053; 13 audio files (WAV)
  - Succalamma, 2002, afc2018065_dc058; Musicantica; 11 audio files (WAV)
  - Tarantala: Dance of the Ancient Spider, 2000, afc2018065_dc059; Alessandra Belloni; 16 audio files (WAV)
  - Theater/dance description, 1982-1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/12)
  - De Mi Trova la Semilla Tono de Jesus, undated, AFC 2018/065: SR239; 1 sound cassette: analog
    Performer: Tono de Jesus. Publisher: San Jose Records 002.
  - [Untitled], 2007, afc2018065_dc057; Newpoli; 12 audio files (WAV)
  - Vincenzo Ancona article in The Clarion, 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/13)
    article by Sciorra.
  - Vincenzo Ancona correspondence, 1985-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 31/14)
  - Vincenzo Ancona grant, 1987-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Subseries 1. Rap, Hip-hop and Doo-wop, ca. 2001-2011
    - Manuscripts and photographs
      - Doo-wop article (Sciorra), 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/2)
      - Doo-wop images, afc2018065_dc045; 10 photographs (TIF, JPG)
      - Doo-wop symposium, 1/2, 2001-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/3)
      - Doo-wop symposium, 2/2, 2001-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/4)
      - Doo-wop/Rock n' Roll bibliography, 1991-2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/5)
      - Hip hop, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/6)
      - Hip wop, 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/7)
      - Hip-hop paper, "Took a Bird to the Boot," 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/8)
      - Hip-hop talk notes, 2002-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/9)
      - "In the Tradition: Black Music From the Bronx" concert series, 1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/10)
      - Italian American Hip-hop, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/11)
      - Mob Candy magazine and correspondence, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/12)
      - Rap/hip-hop themes, ca. 2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/13)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, 4pm, ca. 1990-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/14)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Alpha Male Gorillas, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/15)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, BL. One, ca. 1990-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/16)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Carmine Gotti Music Group, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/17)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Carvelli, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 32/18)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Casa Italiana (2002), 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/1)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Cost'Ovest, ca. 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/2)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, DJ Italian Steve, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/3)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Don Pigro, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/4)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Doo Wittle, 2004-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/5)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Eamon, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/6)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Elemental Magazine, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/7)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Eye-Italian Flava (Oct. 5th) symposium, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/8)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, First Cousins, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/9)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, G Fella, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/10)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Guido Rap, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/11)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Gustapo, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/12)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Hip-hop symposium letters, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/13)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian American Hip-hop brochure and symposium, 2001-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/14)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian American Hip-hop fundraising, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/15)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian American Hip-hop talk, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/16)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian Hip-hop movement, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/17)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian Ice, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/18)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Italian Princess, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/19)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Joe Genovese, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/20)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Johnny Blanco, 2002-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/21)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Jojo Pellegrino, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/22)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Kousin Capone, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/23)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, LaMonphe, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/24)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Little Vic, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/25)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Lordz of Brooklyn, 2006-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/26)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Manifest, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/27)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Marco Polo, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/28)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Mikie Da Poet, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/29)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, mirK maN, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/30)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Northern State, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/31)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, "OC" the Street Pizon, ca. 2006-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/32)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Papa Joe, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 33/33)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Real Goombattas, 2002-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/1)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Real Tru'z (Christian Rap), 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/2)
        article by Sciorra
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Rico Blox, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/3)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Ritrovato, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/4)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Salese, 2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/5)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Scavone, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/6)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, the CHopFather, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/7)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, The Family Album, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/8)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, The Shark, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/9)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Tone Fazoolz, 2008-2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/10)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Vinnie D. and Co., 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/11)
      - Rap/Hip-hop, Vocab Malone, ca. 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/12)
      - Sciorra Rap/Hip-hop paper presentations, 2007-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/13)
    - Audio and video materials
      - Advance Tracks, afc2018065_dc017; DooWittle; 3 audio files (WAV)
      - Backflips and Burnouts, afc2018065_dc010; Alpha Male Gorillas; 5 audio files (WAV)
      - The Brooklyn Way, 2006, afc2018065_dc054; Lordz of Brooklyn; 12 audio files (WAV)
      - The Brooklyn Way, 2006, afc2018065_dc081; Lordz of Brooklyn; 15 video files (VOB, IFO, BUP)
      - Can You Spare a Dime?, afc2018065_dc056; BL. One; 5 audio files (WAV)
      - Casa Nostra: Vol. 1, Desert Storm, afc2018065_dc026; Genovese; 18 audio files (WAV)
      - Exclusive Illseed Shit, afc2018065_dc001; Gustapo; 16 audio files (WAV)
      - Fire EP, afc2018065_dc022; Manifest; 16 audio files (WAV)
      - Graffiti Roc, 2003, afc2018065_dc033; Lordz of Brooklyn; 17 audio files (WAV)
      - The Grilt Cheez EP, afc2018065_dc034; Lil' Man; 23 audio files (WAV)
      - International Playa, 2000, afc2018065_dc020; Giustizia; 8 audio files (WAV)
      - In Tha Mix: The Art of a Champion, 2001-2004, afc2018065_dc018; Giustizia; 15 audio files (WAV)
      - The Italian EP, 2006, afc2018065_dc012; Cost'Ovest; 8 audio files (WAV)
      - JoJo Pellegrino video clips, afc2018065_dc015; JoJo Pellegrino; 5 video files (MOV, AVI, MP4, M4V)
      - JoJo Pellegrino video clips, afc2018065_dc016; JoJo Pellegrino; 4 video files (MOV, MP4, AVI, WMV)
      - La Pinuzza EP, afc2018065_dc011; Cost'Ovest; 5 audio files (WAV)
      - Let's Take It Home! Hosted by DJ Delz, afc2018065_dc024; G Fella; 23 audio files (WAV)
      - Lordz of Brooklyn music videos, afc2018065_dc028; Lordz of Brooklyn; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Mini-mix for Papa Joe, afc2018065_dc023; Cost'Ovest; 3 audio files (WAV)
      - Miscellaneous Italian American Hip Hop, afc2018065_dc047; 6 audio files (WAV)
      - Mixtape 1, afc2018065_dc004; Kuhpretto; 14 audio files (WAV)
      - Music video clips, 2009, afc2018065_dc048; Akhenaton, JoJo Pellegrino, Turi Listen; 6 video files (MOV)
      - My America, afc2018065_dc003; Genovese; 21 audio files (WAV)
      - A Queens Tale, afc2018065_dc041; BL. One; 19 audio files (WAV)
      - Real Goombattas, afc2018065_dc005; 6 audio files (WAV)
      - Sempri Fatt"n Casa (Forever Home Made), 2007, afc2018065_dc013; Cost'Ovest; 16 audio files (WAV)
      - Shine, 2011, afc2018065_dc029; Vesuvo; 11 audio files (WAV)
      - Throw Away Joontz: Tha Mixtape, 2007, afc2018065_dc025; Marco Polo; 21 audio files (WAV)
      - TMR Crew, 1998, afc2018065_dc039; BL. One; 8 audio files (WAV)
      - Tony Soprano video, 2006, afc2018065_dc038; G. Fella; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Trailer, 2007, afc2018065_dc037; Crew; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - [Untitled], 2000, afc2018065_dc021; Manifest; 3 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], 2000-2001, afc2018065_dc027; Don Pigro; 18 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc019; Manifest; 20 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc035; Don Pigro; 4 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc014; JoJo Pellegrino; 4 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc035; JoJo Pellegrino; 21 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc036; JoJo Pellegrino; 12 audio files (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc042; Charlie Zdravesky; 1 audio file (WAV)
      - [Untitled], afc2018065_dc043; Charlie Zdravesky; 1 audio file (WAV)
      - What's Your Mind On?, 2003, afc2018065_dc002; Gustapo; 2 audio files (WAV)
      - Who I Am, afc2018065_dc046; Genovese; 1 audio file (WAV)
- Series 4. Fieldwork and research about New York City neighborhoods, ca. 1981-2017
  Research and fieldwork about neighborhoods in Brooklyn, Queens, and Manhattan, including about immigrant communities, gentrification, environmental issues, and businesses.
  - Adolfo Profumo - Cooper Park Health Info, 1990-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/14)
  - Article about New York City's ethnic social clubs in City Lore magazine, 1991-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/15)
    article by Sciorra and Steve Zeitlin
  - Artists and musicians in Brooklyn, 1988-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/16)
  - Astoria, Queens, ca. 1982-1984, 1 folder of manuscripts with 4 contact sheets, black and white (Box-folder 34/17)
  - Astoria, Queens, ca. 1982-1984, AFC 2018/065: PH091; 156 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 61)
  - Auction images, Katrina Thomas, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH072; 7 slides, color (35mm) (Box 59)
  - Belmont, Bronx, 1985-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/18)
  - Brooklyn - "The Brand," 2002-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/19)
  - Brooklyn - chain stores, 2001-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/20)
  - Brooklyn - displacement, pool, and wrecked buildings, 2006-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/21)
  - Brooklyn - Domino Sugar preservation, 2007-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/22)
  - Brooklyn - gentrification and religion, 2010-2018, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/23)
  - Brooklyn - Religion, 2007-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/24)
  - Brooklyn clashes - hipsters and old school communities, ca. 1984-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/25)
  - Brooklyn housing/development, 1986-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 34/26)
  - Brooklyn lifestyles, 2000-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Brooklyn lofts in industrial zones, 1999-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Brooklyn maps, 1990-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Brooklyn maps, 1995-1998, afc2018065_dc064; 8 photographs (AI, EPS)
  - Brooklyn Neighborhood Book, 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Brooklyn neighborhood politics and politicians, 1983-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Brooklyn neighborhoods, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Brooklyn neighborhoods, 2000-2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Brooklyn neighborhoods - Greenpoint and Williamsburg, 1987-2016, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/8)
  - Brooklyn newsletters and magazines, 2000-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Brooklyn parishes, ca. 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/10)
  - Brooklyn Queens Expressway construction, ca. 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/11)
  - Brooklyn stoops, awnings, and vinyl siding, 2001-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/12)
  - (Brooklyn) environment, oil spill, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/13)
  - Brooklyn, ethnic tensions, 1975-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/14)
  - Brooklyn: "New Bohemia," ca. 1992-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/15)
  - Brooklyn: Individuals and real estate, 2000-2015, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/16)
  - Brooklyn: Neighborhood - crime, ca. 1983-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 35/17)
  - Brooklyn: Neighborhood - sports, ca. 1987-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Brooklyn: Williamsburg's "Subsidized Young," 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Bushwick (Brooklyn) gentrified, 2009-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Carroll Gardens, Brooklyn, 2002-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Closing Engine 212 Firehouse, 2000-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Cooper Park House/Devoe Street Baptist Church, 1991-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Districts, New York, 1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/7)
  - East Harlem, Manhattan, 2002-2011, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/8)
  - East New York, 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Ethnicity in the Public Schools, Brooklyn Historical Society, 1986-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 1/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 2/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 3/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 4/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 5/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Fieldwork notebooks, 6/6, ca. 1981-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Foreigners in Williamsburg, 2003-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Greenpoint articles, 1982-1984, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Greenpoint gentrified (articles), 1986-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Greenpoint hospital, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Greenpoint warehouse fire, 2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Hasidic and Latino conflict, 1987-1999, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Hazardous Neighbors? Living Next Door to Industry in Greenpoint-Williamsburg (a Hunter College report), 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/9)
  - Hipster views of Italian Williamsburg, 2008-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Hipsters, 2005-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/11)
  - Hipsters beyond Brooklyn, Hipsturbia article, 2010-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/12)
  - Hispanic Good Friday processions, 1992-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Hispanic Williamsburg, 1991-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Housing, especially Italian American, 1981-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 37/15)
  - Italian American empowerment, 1993-1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Italian Folk Arts survey of Nassau and Queens slides, 1986-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH086; 28 slides, color (35mm) (Box 60)
  - Italian neighborhood markers, ca. 1994-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts with 5 photographic prints, color (3.5x5) (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Italian neighborhood markers, ca. 1994-2007, AFC 2018/065: PH089; 16 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 61)
  - Italian neighborhood markers, ca. 1994-2007, AFC 2018/065: PH003; 16 slides, color (Box 47)
  - Italian neighborhoods (NYC) walking tours, 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Italian neighborhoods, Brooklyn, 1983-1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Block associations, 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Columbus Day Parade, 1985-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Columbus Day Parade, AFC 2018/065: PH042; 23 slides, color (35mm) (Box 53)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Individuals, 1999-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Italian Baptist church, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Manhattan Special, 1983-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/9)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Parks, Squares, and Triangles, 2007-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/10)
  - Italian Williamsburg - POWs Camp WWII, 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/11)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Restaurants, 1984-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/12)
  - Italian Williamsburg - School Settlement Association, 2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/13)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Swinging Sixties Senior Citizen Center, 1983-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/14)
  - Italian Williamsburg - Via Vespucci, 1976-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/15)
  - Italian Williamsburg descriptions and accounts, 1979-2016, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/16)
  - Italian WR91 Mosque, 1991-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/17)
  - Italians in NYC, statistics, 2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/18)
  - Jewish lights, 2006, 1 folder of manuscripts with 8 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 38/19)
  - Jewish lights, 2006, AFC 2018/065: PH121; 8 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
  - Latinos, Williamsburg, 2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/20)
  - Lithuanian Americans, 1991-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/21)
  - Little Italy, Manhattan, 2000-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/22)
  - Long Island City (Queens), 1999, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/23)
  - Lynbrook, St. Anthony's with picnic, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH068; 1 slide, color (35mm) (Box 58)
  - Nassau-Queens original slideshow #1 (1-72), 1986-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH083; 42 slides, color (35mm) (Box 59-60)
    Many images by Martha Cooper.
  - Nassau-Queens original slideshow #2 (73-139), 1986-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH084; 64 slides, color (35mm) (Box 60)
  - Nassau-Queens original slideshow #3 (140-224), 1986-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH085; 85 slides, color (35mm) (Box 60)
  - Neighborhood - "Polish Greenpoint" articles, ca. 1982-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 38/24)
  - Neighborhood - What's in a Name?, 1987-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts with 1 photographic print, color (4x6) (Box-folder 38/25)
  - Neighborhood (Brooklyn) - women (Organization of Neighborhood Women/Metropolitan Ave), 1983-1997, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/1)
  - Neighborhood, Brooklyn - Pollution, folder 1/2, 1990-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/2)
  - Neighborhood, Brooklyn - Pollution, folder 2/2, 1990-1998, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/3)
  - New York City at the Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/4)
  - New York Council for the Humanities, 1990-1999, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/5)
  - New York immigrant communities: Queens guide, ca. 1985-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts with 3 contact sheets, black and white (Box-folder 39/6)
  - New York immigrant communities: Queens guide, ca. 1985-1993, AFC 2018/065: PH097; 126 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 62)
  - New York neighborhoods: Brooklyn demographics, 2002-2010, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 46/6)
  - New York State bills passed, OLMC of Rosebank, 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/7)
  - New York State Council on the Arts, 1985-1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Organized tours in NYC, 1989-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Ornamental iron worker, 1998-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Casita photo essays, 1990, 1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Casita presentations and papers, ca. 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Casitas slides and photographic prints, ca. 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts with 18 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 39/13)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Casitas slides and photographic prints, ca. 1988, AFC 2018/065: PH011; 94 slides, color (Box 48)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Comite journal, 33543, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/14)
  - Puerto Rican communities: Return to the Future (Sciorra article), 1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/15)
  - Queens - Nassau slide show, #1, ca. 1987, AFC 2018/065: PH065; 135 slides, color (35mm) (Box 57-58)
    photos by Martha Cooper, and Joseph Sciorra
  - Queens - Nassau slide show, #2, ca. 1987, AFC 2018/065: PH066; 79 slides, color (35mm) (Box 57-58)
    photos by Joseph Sciorra, Lillian Caruana, Marsha Weinstein, and Martha Cooper
  - Queens: Ozone Park, Astoria, 1990-2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/16)
  - Religion in NYC/USA, 2005 (Box-folder 39/17)
  - Rezoning and condos, buildings, 2001-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/18)
  - Ridgewood (Queens), 2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/19)
  - Saving Mt. Manresa, Staten Island, 2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/20)
  - Sciorra articles in New York Folklore newsletter, 1985-1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 39/21)
  - Secret Lives of New York - Dinitia Smith article, 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Three Kings Day Parade, 2005-2018, 1 folder of manuscripts with 29 color photographic prints (4x6) (Box-folder 40/2)
    29 photographic prints, color (4x6)
  - Three Kings Day Parade, 2005-2018, AFC 2018/065: PH122; 50 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 64)
  - Unidentified slides, ca. 1986-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH069; 48 slides, color (35mm) (Box 58)
  - Williamsburg - food, 1996-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Williamsburg - L Train, 2001-2017, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Williamsburg - McCarren Park Pool, 1999-2012, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Williamsburg (Brooklyn), New York Times articles, 1986-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Williamsburg clubs, 1990-2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/7)
  - The Williamsburg Neighborhood Profile (book), 1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 40/8)